Oh, oh excuse me just having a little liquid refreshment.
This here is a mug.
And it says on here in German words or something.
And on the bottom it says Avon.
I don't know if you saw one of mine but we talked about Avon once.
And this is, has got a tag that's in that, remember I mentioned it was the foil tag?
This is a made in Japan Avon mug.
So it's still cute.
I'm not big on mugs but this is a newer made in Japan Avon mug.
I would say, I don't know, probably the 70's, 60's.
Now let's take a look at the common yucky Japan mugs that you find these everywhere.
You don't want to buy these if you find them because they're pretty much worth nothing but everybody thinks they're great.
If you want to put them away for 20, 30 years, don't count on this for retirement.
Okay.
Then let's talk about, this is an interesting concept here.
This is one of my favorites because I like Las Vegas collectibles.
This is a Japan, and that's a whole other topic, a whole other documentary, Las Vegas collectibles.
This is an old casino that used to be downtown that no longer is.
But isn't it cute?
And it's a made in Japan mug.
So made in Japan.
Many uses.
Some are more collectible than others given the topic or who it is or what it does.
So remember, Japan, bottoms up.